♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 1=
♪Under your feet♪
♪Is the Night Spring Path
of life and death♪
♪Seen from where you stand♪
♪Is the Lethe River of this life♪
♪Over the river♪
♪Is the Nepenthe Bridge
of the disappearing past♪
♪At the end of the river♪
♪Is the Karma Stone of the lost destiny♪
You Jun.
What are you singing?
(Yin)
Yin,
why are you back again?
Yin?
I gave you a new life in the mortal world
only about 17 or 18 years ago
(Xiu Yan)
and I made you a princess.
Why was it over so soon?
Is it that even the imperial power
can't smother your bad luck?
Don't you remember what you said?
Before you sent me to the mortal world,
you promised
that I would enjoy a long and happy life.
But what happened?
My biological brother killed me.
Such a lousy life.
So, it's easy to bribe the King of Hell
while it's hard to bribe his subordinates.
This path,
I've experienced it over twenty times.
When can I stop doing this?
Who is he?
He looks distinguished.
What's so great about him?
But why does he look
so sad?
I know.
I heard a thousand years ago,
the female immortal he adored
fell in love with the Fox King.
She helped the Fox King
to destroy the Spirit Mountain
of the Immortal Realm
and started a war
between immortals and demons.
In front of all the armies,
he killed his beloved immortal
with his magic weapon.
So, every year, he comes here
to see if he can find
a little bit of residual spirit of hers.
He killed her
but still doesn't leave her alone.
Rather ruthless.
He's just seeking psychological comfort.
You're right.
He killed her, anyway.
Why would he not let it go?
If I were that female immortal,
I would never see him again,
alive or dead.
I should go.
By the way,
what is the name
of the female immortal
You Jun just mentioned?
Yin.
Her name, I mean.
Her name is
Yin.
(Yuan Qi)
Xiu Yan,
was that Yin?
Yin no longer exists in this world.
Don't you remember?
Your Spirit Sword is a supreme weapon.
How could anyone survive it?
It was just your hallucination.
Yin,
we will meet again.
(A thousand years ago)
(Wutong Island, the Immortal Realm)
- Senior brother.
I've mastered
the magic you taught me.
(Feng Yuan, Heavenly Empress
and Phoenix Queen)
Girl,
you've been nurtured in there
for a hundred years.
Finally, you're coming out.
The Three Realms
have been uneventful for so long.
It's time to have a celebration.
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
On our own island,
call me "Your Ladyship".
- Aye.
At my command, go tell the world
that we will hold a large banquet
to celebrate
the birth of the second Fire Phoenix.
(Daze Mountain, the Immortal Realm)
(Invitation)
(It is a great thing for Wutong Island
to have a second Fire Phoenix.)
(You're invited to come
for the celebration of her birth.)
(Donghua, Chief of Daze Mountain)
After the Ancestral God built the world,
a new Fire Phoenix was never born
until the old one died.
This has never happened before
that a Fire Phoenix is born
when the Phoenix Queen is still alive.
I guess Feng Yuan
can't wait to leave the Phoenix Clan
to the young Fire Phoenix
and then live a simple life herself.
- Greetings, Martial Uncle Xian Zhu.
(Xian Zhu, Disciple of Daze Mountain)
Master, the presents are ready.
Gu Jin is an old friend of the Phoenix Queen.
We'll send him.
It's about time.
Where is Gu Jin?
I sent my man searching.
(Zuixian Tavern, the Immortal Realm)
This is the Immortal Brew,
very rare wine.
Here's the last jar.
Guests,
make an offer.
I'll offer
a straw of Tortoise-snake Ganoderma
from Wanyi Island.
Eat it
(Ling Feng, Young Master of Wanyi Mountain)
and your life will be prolonged.
What's so great about that?
I'll offer something
that no one else will.
That is,
my cultivation base of 200 years.
Base of 200 years?
Gu Jin,
you're just being
deliberately perverse, huh?
You bought all the Immortal Brew
every time it was sold.
Stop being so selfish, will you?
Whoever offers more
gets it.
(Gu Jin, Disciple of Daze Mountain)
I'm fine.
Who is he?
Madam,
I'm from Daze Mountain,
a decent immortal sect.
My spiritual power of 200 years
is enough for the wine, isn't it?
Deal.
Thank you.
Spiritual power of 200 years...
Gu Jin,
for some wine,
you don't even care
for the reputation of your sect.
How could Lord Donghua
have such a useless disciple like you?
Only someone who hasn't tasted it
would ask such a silly question.
Someone who tasted it would only say,
"Tastes great."
Have some taste.
Whatever.
Martial Uncle. Martial Uncle.
I've found you at last.
(Qing Yun, Disciple of Daze Mountain)
Oh, Qing Yun.
You're just in time.
Give the landlady
my cultivation base of 200 years.
200...
What? 200 years?
Madam, what...
Martial Uncle.
He's your new disciple?
Yes.
(Xian Shan, Disciple of Daze Mountain)
This young man has just become an immortal.
I thought he had some potential,
so I took him as my disciple.
All right. An immortal name for you,
Qing Yi.
(Qing Yi, Disciple of Daze Mountain)
Kneel and say thank you
to your grandmaster.
Thank you, Grandmaster.
You may rise.
Cultivate hard
and you will have a brilliant future.
On Daze Mountain,
you can learn from anyone
but your Martial Uncle Gu Jin
who is rather naughty.
Never
copy him.
Master, Grandmaster.
Grandmaster, I found Martial Uncle Gu Jin.
What happened to him?
On the Immortal Avenue,
he gambled for wine
and lost all his spiritual power
of 200 years.
What... What?
But he's only 200 years old.
Exactly.
I pleaded with the landlady
and gave her a lot of magic tools.
I didn't manage to get him back
until I promised her
that you would inscribe her tavern.
Ridiculous.
So naughty.
Master,
it's getting late.
Don't bother to punish him
before he's back from Wutong Island.
Well,
you can take the Snow-shaft Carriage.
Qing Yi.
You've just been here.
Go with your Martial Uncle
to broaden your vision.
Yes, Grandmaster.
Qing Yi,
watch your Martial Uncle.
Don't let him disgrace us.
Qing Yi,
you're so lucky.
As soon as you came,
you became a disciple of Daze Mountain.
Do you know we are
the first-class immortal sect?
First-class immortal sect?
So, are we the most powerful?
In the entire world,
ancient gods are the most powerful.
Below the God Realm
and above the Mortal Realm,
there are the Three Lower Realms,
the Immortal Realm, the Demon Realm,
and the Nether Realm.
The God Realm
is where true gods live.
You can't get up there
until you become a god.
But too bad.
The gate of the God Realm
hasn't been open for years.
I used to think
immortals were the best we could be.
I didn't know we could even be gods.
Then, are immortals
under the control of gods?
Yes.
And no.
Everything in this world
goes its own way.
The Three Realms
have their own rulers.
Gods
seldom interfere.
Master,
did you send Gu Jin to Wutong Island
because of his identity?
In the Three Lower Realms,
no one knows
Gu Jin is the son of two true gods
except you, the Heavenly Empress,
Chief of Qingchi Palace,
and me.
200 years ago,
the Destruction Tribulation appeared.
To save the world,
Yuan Qi's father True God Di Juan
sacrificed his life.
(Young Yuan Qi)
His mother True Goddess Yi He was so sad
that she sealed up the God Realm,
trying to get True God Di Juan back to life.
Yuan Qi was frustrated.
- For some unknown reason,
- Mother.
he lost all his god power.
Mother.
Then his mother
- sent him down here for experience.
- Don't leave me.
Fire Phoenix is the spirit beast of true gods.
The one to be born
is deeply related to Gu Jin.
So, this time,
he has to go personally.
Save the world?
It's awesome to be a god.
What's so great about being a god?
Quite cold.
Boring.
Martial Uncle, you've been there before?
No.
I guessed.
New immortal?
Yes, Martial Uncle.
Fine.
Since you call me Martial Uncle,
I'll look out for you.
Martial Uncle,
you've lost
your spiritual power of 200 years.
How can you look out for me?
Just a little power.
You'll know.
Immortals like us have nothing
but plenty of time.
Spiritual power of 200 years.
Soon, I can get it back.
I don't care.
Come on, Martial Uncle.
Don't mention it.
Master has got it back
for you.
Take it.
Thank you, Master.
You actually care, don't you?
Better than nothing.
Well,
if someone bullies you,
I may fail to protect you.
But speaking of seeking pleasure,
count on me.
Ling Feng,
isn't that the Snow-shaft Carriage
the late Heavenly Emperor
gave Lord Donghua?
His useless disciple
must be sitting in it.
Let's play a trick on him.
What's going on?
- The horse…
- Qing Yun,
stop the horse.
Ling Feng?
Oh, Wan Yi.
(Cangwu Hall, Wutong Island)
Long time no see.
Come on. Get in there.
Dragon King of the East Sea,
long time no see.
Come in, please.
(Feng Yin)
(This is the celebration of my birth.)
(I can't miss out on this.)
(No one can recognize me now.)
Your Majesty,
has the pretty wife for my nephew
come out?
How daring!
Demon Lord Hong Ruo,
this is a celebration of immortals.
How could you mess it up?
For your information, Dragon King,
Demon Lord Hong Ruo
has been an old friend of our queen.
She's here to give her blessing.
(Hong Ruo, Fox Queen)
The invitation
was sent to you three days ago.
What have you been doing these days?
When I was passing the sea
under the jurisdiction
of Dragon King Ao Lin,
I saw Nine-headed Snakes do the crime.
I had an itch
and killed them.
Dragon King,
- your jurisdiction isn't that safe.
- You!
- She satirized Dragon King in his face.
- Forget it.
Come on.
You're as tough as before.
Today is the day
Feng Yin will come out.
Don't forget.
Back on Jingyou Mountain,
you lost to me
and promised
I could pick any phoenix
to be my nephew's wife.
Look.
I've even brought
a betrothal present.
Even if you offered your whole clan
as the bride price,
that wouldn't be enough.
Now,
you try to kid me
with a mere core of a Nine-headed Snake.
Don't you fear I'd destroy your den?
It's just a welcome gift.
When Feng Yin becomes an adult,
I'll come with the betrothal gifts.
You're the Heavenly Empress.
Don't go back on your word.
Your Majesty,
you can't do this.
Fire Phoenix is our queen.
How can she marry a demon?
Yeah.
- This is ridiculous.
- She can't.
How can demons and immortals get married?
Who said I would marry
a female immortal?
(Hong Yi, Fox Queen's Nephew)
If I had known your purpose,
I wouldn't have come with you.
Hong Yi.
Don't make decisions for me.
Now, I don't want to get engaged.
Even if I did,
I could choose
from millions of female demons.
Isn't it better
than flattering the immortals?
Hong Yi,
don't be so rude.
(This demon is quite short-tempered.)
(Does he have a grudge against immortals?)
Your nephew
has your temper.
Young man,
even if you don't want to get married,
you shouldn't waste
your aunt's care for you.
You have to know,
the more you talk, the more you'll regret.
Are you leaving or not?
Hong Yi.
Hong Yi!
We're here, anyway.
Forget about the marriage thing.
There are also many powerful immortals
in the Immortal Realm.
If you can
make some friends
and learn from them,
your trip will be worthwhile.
Such a waste of time.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
- Martial Uncle.
Martial Uncle.
Is this the powerful immortal
you just talked about?
What can I learn from him?
Hong Yi,
don't be disrespectful.
Who are you?
What are you talking about?
None of your business.
What do you think you're doing?
Do you know
who you just
flung?
This is
a great disciple
of Lord Donghua on Daze Mountain.
If you dare,
have a competition with him.
No need.
I don't want that.
I'm here for the banquet,
not the competition.
Are you leaving or not?
If you still want to stay
and flatter these immortals,
I'll go alone.
Hong Yi!
Don't go.
You hurt Lord Donghua's disciple.
You can't get away like this.
Young Master Ling Feng,
since when did you defend me like that?
I have something to say
to that demon.
If you catch up with him
and get him back,
I will give you
some Immortal Brew.
Are you sure?
You can do
the Cloud-sticking Trick.
Then I really wonder
why you need the Cloud-riding Talisman
on the bottom of your shoe.
You tricked me!
You burned my carriage, right?
- Yes. So what?
- Stop.
Jin,
Her Majesty is watching.
Don't make a fool.
All right, everybody. Go take your seat.
Go.
(Who is this man?)
(Cangwu Hall)
Peacock King Hua Mo
and Princess Hua Shu have arrived.
Get them in.
(Hua Mo, Peacock King)
(Hua Shu, Peacock Princess)
This is my daughter, Hua Shu.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
There's no need for that.
We haven't met for many years.
Your pretty daughter
has been more charming.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Take your seats.
Qing Yun,
are all female immortals
so gorgeous?
No female immortal in this hall
can be as beautiful
as Hua Shu.
You regret being engaged with Bi Yun, huh?
Hua Shu is beautiful.
But if the young Fire Phoenix
is far more charming,
don't you need to break off again?
Right, I should think this through.
Peacocks are of a second-class immortal sect.
But they're always arrogant.
Look at her.
She wears the Elliptic Peacock Jade
to show off.
She doesn't know
there's a Fire Phoenix Jade
from True Goddess Yi He
and that's truly valuable.
When it appears,
the Elliptic Peacock Jade
will be eclipsed.
When the young Fire Phoenix is born,
no one will notice the peacock.
My guests,
cheers.
Instead of staying in the shell,
you fly around
with the Transformation Trick
I taught you.
Tell me.
Why did you fly out?
If I hadn't come out,
I wouldn't know
who you'd marry me to.
Oh, Master.
I'll make my own decision
in marriage.
No one can arrange anything for me.
I don't know
who you got this temper from.
You.
I have a question.
Are immortals
destined to be
inferior or superior?
Why do you ask?
I just met some female immortals.
They all want to marry someone powerful.
Some male immortals
are the same.
They compare family property
as if that was everything.
I don't quite understand.
Others can think this way,
but you can't.
Because you're born to be a queen.
How could you know what others suffer?
Then I've made up my mind.
I won't be a queen as soon as I'm born.
I'm going to travel around
and experience hardships in life
before I come back
and fairly compete with my clansmen
for the throne.
You think it's so easy
to take the throne?
Every Fire Phoenix
has to go through countless disasters.
You never know
what you'll have to suffer
after you're born.
(Abyssal Prison)
Master,
a lot of guests are on Wutong Island.
So, the barrier has been inactivated.
I can sneak in
and wait to kill.
In two hours,
(Zhuo Ying, Devil)
the Fire Phoenix will be born.
She must be
having the Fire Phoenix Jade.
It's been 200 years.
I've been waiting too long
for this day.
Immortals and demons
sealed me in the Abyssal Prison.
Feng Yuan was in on it, too.
(Qing Lin)
Snatch the Fire Phoenix Jade
and kill that young phoenix.
You promised
to propose to me on this year's birthday.
Why haven't you come yet?
Are you trying to get Hua Shu?
I saw you stare at her
even with your eyes sparkling.
I... I was eyeing her for Lei Che.
Where are Qing Yi and Qing Yun?
It's such a big garden.
What if they get lost?
Today, most young immortals came here
for the young Fire Phoenix.
But in my opinion,
you're just dreaming.
Fire Phoenix
is the spirit beast of true gods.
Except for Yuan Qi,
the only young god,
who else can be good enough for her?
He's a true god, but so what?
He's been living in the God Realm
and no one has seen him.
Maybe he's ugly
and the young Fire Phoenix won't like him.
How dare you slander a true god?
Don't be scared.
The gate of the God Realm is closed.
Besides,
Yuan Qi
just has a better family
than us.
But since he was born,
he's never got love from his parents.
Shh.
And I heard
a lot of things happened in the God Realm.
His mother Yi He
had a love affair
with an immortal.
Maybe,
Yuan Qi isn't their biological son.
True God Di Juan died
possibly because he realized
that Yuan Qi
wasn't his real son.
Out of anger, he jumped
into the Destruction Tribulation
and earned a reputation.
Shut up!
Who are you?
How dare you say that?
It's you again. None of your business!
True God Di Juan died for the world.
You aren't even qualified to talk about him.
I rule my own mouth.
- I can say whatever I like.
- Ling Feng...
Ling Feng, don't.
Ling Feng, stop.
With such little power,
you dare to defend a true god, huh?
You're in over your head!
Darn it!
Put me down!
Put him down.
He heard what you just said.
If this gets out,
we'll be in trouble.
Oh, you reminded me.
What are you doing?
He heard our conversation.
If I don't erase his memories,
he'll tell other people
and we'll be in trouble.
You aren't even a junior immortal yet.
Only a senior immortal
can use the Memory-erasure Trick.
If anything goes wrong,
you may hurt his spirit.
Don't worry.
I saw how my father used it.
It didn't look very hard.
I should at least
erase half of his memory.
Screw you!
Stop.
Who?
Who's interfering?
Put me down!
(Red dress?)
Ling Feng.
Are you Princess Hua Shu?
Hua Shu?
Your Highness,
Ling Feng just lost his mind.
He didn't really mean that.
Your Highness,
Gu Jin and I were just playing.
Don't take it seriously.
Princess Hua Shu?
A woman saved your life.
You must be too ashamed to tell others.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
did you just help me out?
(So,)
(he mistook me)
(for the immortal in the corner.)
I'm Gu Jin from Daze Mountain.
Just a little favor.
It's not even worth mentioning.
So, it's really you.
Thank you for helping me out.
Some stain.
Thank you.
Without you, Your Highness,
I would have been injured today.
I will return the favor.
No need.
It's nothing. Forget it.
I can't.
Master told me
to be always grateful.
If you want anything, Your Highness,
let me know.
I will get it for you.
That's some tough talk.
(Hongque, Maid of the Peacock Clan)
Can you really get
whatever Her Highness wants?
Of course.
Fine. I've heard
the young Fire Phoenix has
the Fire Phoenix Jade from True Goddess Yi He.
This is
what you can't get.
Fire Phoenix Jade.
Is that what you want, Your Highness?
I just want to take a look.
You're young and inexperienced.
You shouldn't have promised casually.
Wait.
I... I can get it.
I'm on my way
to get the jade for you.
Farewell.
Your Highness...
Why did you admit
that you helped him?
But it wasn't you.
Daze Mountain will owe me.
Why would I reject that?
Maybe,
I'll need him someday.
(Sizzling Fire Barrier.)
(No wonder I couldn't break it,)
(however hard I try.)
(His blood can break the barrier.)
Who are you?
What's going on?
I don't want your spiritual power.
Fire Phoenix Jade?
It's Feng Yin.
Martial Uncle.
All her immortal spirit
is gone.
Gone?
What?
Aunt...
Your Majesty.
Soul-burning Lamp.
I'll go with you.
Not even a smell
of Feng Yin's immortal spirit
is in the Three Realms.
I'm afraid...
She was smashed by the Fire Phoenix Jade
and fell into the turbulence
of time and space.
What were you doing here
in Feng Yin's habitat?
I was just trying
to see her Fire Phoenix Jade.
Why did you want to see that?
I...
I was out of the barrier.
I didn't know why,
but some force
pulled me into the barrier.
I... I controlled myself
with the Immortal-locking Spell.
But out of nowhere,
someone in black rushed out
and cut my Immortal-locking Rope.
So, I was pulled in here.
The Fire Phoenix Jade
seemed to be startled
and it suddenly exploded.
Go check it out
if this man is still on the island.
Your Majesty,
we have a Fire Phoenix
every tens of thousands of years.
Now, she's dead for no reason.
Please punish him
with the Bone-cutting Thunder Strike.
Yeah, Your Majesty.
He's Lord Donghua's disciple,
but he killed the queen of our clan.
We are
sworn enemies!
- We're sworn enemies!
Your Majesty,
whatever I explain,
the young Fire Phoenix lost her life
because of my rash move.
I'm ready for any punishment.
Your Majesty,
please show some mercy.
No need.
Any punishment will do.
You...
How can I explain to your master
or your parents?
No matter who I am,
I have to answer for what I did.
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪