♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 2=
Your Majesty.
Please show some mercy.
All elders.
I foresaw
that my disciple was naughty
and had gotten into trouble.
That's why I'm here.
I'd like to ask all of you
to give him a chance
to make amends
for the sake of me.
How to make amends?
Her Majesty has checked
with the Soul-burning Lamp.
Feng Yin's immortal spirit
has been torn apart.
There's no trace of it in the Three Realms.
There will be no day of reunion.
I have a Soul Suppressing Pagoda,
which is an ancient artifact.
Although Immortal Feng's
immortal spirit dispersed,
her physical body remains there.
If her physical body
is contained here,
it will not decay.
In the future, if Immortal Feng's
immortal spirit is returned,
she can be exempted from
thousands of years of cultivation.
I also know
that there is another Soul Suppressing Pagoda
in the Nether Realm.
If the two pagodas summon together,
they may be able
to call back Immortal Feng's
immortal spirit.
Heaven Path.
Master.
I can go to the Heaven Path.
As long as Feng Yin can return,
I'll do anything.
The Heaven Path is the path to the gods.
There is the coercion of the gods.
If you ask anything
from the Heaven Stone,
you have to bear nine Heaven Whips.
The Heaven Whips
will all hit on your spirit.
If you're not a demigod,
I'm afraid
you will fall.
You can never go
to the Heaven Path.
I'm going to go to the Nether Realm
to beg for
another Soul Suppressing Pagoda.
Please
give me a chance.
If it doesn't work,
go ahead and discipline my disciple.
That being the case,
let Lord Donghua give it a try.
(Heaven Path)
♪A tear is tied under the river of hope♪
♪It's a trip to the seasons♪
♪The years are like a dream♪
♪The wind rises,
the thoughts are in the way♪
♪The ink is thick, the past is stained♪
♪The past in dark in light♪
♪The old face of yesteryear♪
♪Diluted in the moment of looking back♪
Honor God with sincerity.
I have what I want.
What the wise man sees,
break through the nameless.
(Gu Jin.)
(No.)
(Young Yuan Qi.)
(Are you here to ask)
(for the young Fire Phoenix?)
Yes.
Heaven Stone.
I want the return
of Fung Yin's immortal spirit.
(Do you realize)
(that whether
you're a lowly immortal)
(or a true god,)
(it takes a great deal)
(to get to ask anything
from the Heaven Stone?)
Yes.
But if I hadn't happened
to be nearby at that time,
that person wouldn't have been able
to break through
the Heavenly Empress's Sizzling
Fire Barrier anyway.
It was also because of
the blood of chaos in my body
that the Fire Phoenix Jade
given by Mother
recognized me
and sucked up all the immortal spirit
of the young Fire Phoenix.
It's all my fault.
(A Fire Phoenix)
(has a lifetime
only when it is extinguished.)
(Feng Yin was born in defiance of nature.)
(So her return)
(is even more unnatural.)
(It's not too late for you to regret now.)
I won't regret it.
♪The past is stained♪
I'm willing to do it
whatever it takes.
(Okay.)
(Remember what you said today.)
♪The old face of yesteryear♪
♪Diluted in the moment of looking back♪
♪Drinking all the time♪
(I grant you a catastrophe.)
(You will respond to the catastrophe
with yourself)
(in exchange for the return of Feng Yin.)
♪I want a satisfactory life♪
♪I wish for a next life of love♪
♪I hope to see the flowers
bloom and fade again♪
(Feng Yin's immortal spirit)
(will be regrouped in the Three Realms.)
(If there is a chance,)
(it will return.)
♪Be with you forever♪
(He responds to the catastrophe
with himself.)
(I didn't realize)
(that Feng Yin's return)
(was going)
(to cost Gu Jin so much.)
Is there a cure
for the curse of the Heaven Stone?
The Heaven Stone was set up
by the Ancestral God Qing Tian.
Making a deal with it
is making a promise
to the Ancestral God.
How could there be a cure?
Even if Gu Jin hides in the God Realm,
he can't avoid it.
You don't know
when this catastrophe will come
and in what form.
I'm afraid he'll have to
spend the rest of his life in fear.
True God Di Juan
has not yet awakened.
Yi He
entrusted this child to us back then.
Are we going
to let the true gods' only bloodline
fall into crisis?
I predicted
Gu Jin's destiny last night.
His Catastrophe-relief Gate
lies in the return of Feng Yin.
The karma entwined between them
is by no means so simple.
Anyway,
each generation has its own destiny.
Their destiny
is not for us to decide.
Just go with the flow.
Forget it.
I have gathered all the immortal spirit
of Chen Fang in these two hundred years.
From tomorrow onwards,
I will be in seclusion,
cultivating the immortal spirit
for Chen Fang.
I have temporarily
handed over my position to Lan Feng.
The Three Realms
should be left to the young.
As for the person
Gu Jin said that he didn't know
whether he was a demon or an immortal,
his whereabouts
had not been found so far.
I am afraid that the future
of the Three Realms may not be peaceful.
(Ten years later)
Martial Uncle.
Martial Uncle,
I've brought you some wine.
(Forbidden Valley, Daze Mountain)
Martial Uncle.
Drunken Jade Dew.
Here comes my Drunken Jade Dew.
Qing Yi, I am coming!
(Pass on my order.)
(Gu Jin is so mischievous and misguided)
(that he was grounded in the valley)
(and not allowed to leave.)
Fatty Chi.
You're being way too dutiful.
Her Majesty allowed Qing Yi
to come in for a quarter every month
to bring me food.
It's almost time.
Can't you do me a favor?
(It's still a little short)
(of a month away.)
(Also,)
(please call me Huo Chi. Thank you.)
Huo Chi.
I'll roast you
and eat you one day.
- Qing Yi.
- Martial Uncle.
Drunken Jade Dew.
I've waited so hard for you.
Thank you, Qing Yi.
Martial Uncle, Master said
that his Drunken Jade Dew
is not as good as Immortal Brew.
But there's only so much
as a bucket a year.
It's full of spiritual power.
Take your time.
Drink it sparingly.
Got it.
Am I stuck fishing all the time
again this month?
There's nothing else to do
in the Forbidden Valley.
All right.
Come on.
By the way,
any letter for me?
Letter?
Letter from Princess Hua Shu!
Before I came here,
I wrote a letter to Princess Hua Shu.
I've been here for ten years.
Why hasn't she replied?
Martial Uncle.
You'd better
forget about that letter.
Princess Hua Shu
is the top beauty of the Immortal Realm.
The people who want to marry her
could line up from Bainiao Island
to Daze Mountain.
What?
She's getting married?
No.
It's good that she's still waiting for me.
Her Majesty said that you cannot
leave the Forbidden Valley
until the young Fire Phoenix woke up.
But the young Fire Phoenix
hasn't woken up yet.
When will you be able to leave?
You're all alone here.
I'm really afraid
you'll be mentally ill.
Who can I ask?
It doesn't make sense for the Heaven Stone
to go off the rails.
There are just me
and some unintelligent beasts
in such a big Forbidden Valley.
I feel like if it goes on,
I'm even going to learn the beast language.
It is almost time.
My Drunken Jade Dew!
Fortunately,
it's not broken.
That's good.
Qing Yi.
Hold this for me.
What's this?
This seems to be
an egg of a Water Divine Beast.
Water Divine Beast?
What's that?
Don't you know?
Water Divine Beast
is the entire world's
most nutritious panacea.
Their spiritual core is very nutritious,
and can repair broken internal cores,
and also replenish centuries of immortal power.
Its skin can be used
to treat traumatic injuries,
its bones can be used to treat fire injuries,
and even its nails
can be used as medicine.
It's a pity that the Water Divine Beast Clan
went extinct 70,000 years ago.
I didn't expect to find one
in the Forbidden Valley.
Amazing.
Are you going to eat it, Martial Uncle?
How can I eat it?
How about
giving it to Feng Yin?
Maybe she could wake up earlier.
(Time is up.)
(Get out of here!)
Time is up.
Martial Uncle, I have to go.
I'll come and see you
when your egg hatches.
Let me know
if she replies.
Okay.
How do all those immortal beasts
hatch their eggs?
Is antenatal training needed?
Little guy.
It's my first time hatching an egg
and I don't have much experience.
But
your spiritual core is very important to me.
On the one hand,
you can save Feng Yin.
On the other hand,
my future with Princess Hua Shu
is riding on you.
So you have to work hard.
Hatch yourself out
with me,
okay?
But it's getting late.
Let's work on it tomorrow.
Time to go to bed.
It seems like mothers
like to nest their eggs
in the warmest place possible.
Man.
It's been so long.
Why are you
still so quiet?
Forget it.
Soak in the bath for a while longer.
The marinated meat Qing Yi made
is quite tasty.
Feng Yin has been sleeping for so long.
Would it be too light
to take a core
as soon as she wakes up?
Marinated egg pickling technique.
Anise.
Put some.
Cinnamon, a big one.
Come on.
Bay leaf.
Put some.
Pepper.
Take a dip every day.
By the day you break out of your shell,
I'll have
a spiced core.
(Bad man.)
So that's what you look like.
It's not the same
as in the picture book.
You look
healthier.
Looks like I'm
pretty good at hatching eggs.
Why are you laughing?
You've been running around
since you came out of your shell,
and you went
to the Forbidden Valley.
Listen, the Forbidden Valley
is full of fierce
and uncivilized beasts.
If you run off like that,
what if they eat you?
Your core is mine.
If you get eaten by them,
it's going to be wasted.
Understand?
Why are you crying?
All right, stop crying.
I was just trying to scare you.
Now that you've transformed,
I don't want to take your internal core.
I have a friend.
He is kind of your relative.
How about this?
When you grow up,
let's go ask him for advice.
Just use your spiritual power to save people.
Okay?
All right.
Come on.
I didn't think I'd actually hatch you.
Man.
Why don't you be my spirit beast?
Your cries
are so unpleasant.
Why don't I call you Yin?
Stay put.
Didn't I tell you
not to run around?
Get down.
Don't you run up there.
Don't run around!
It's been six months.
Haven't you tossed enough?
Listen.
From today onwards,
you can't even leave this yard.
I'm so exhausted.
Hungry?
Say something.
And if I am satisfied,
it is yours.
Whatever.
Let me tell you.
If you don't eat, you'll be hungry.
I've had enough.
I'm going to sleep.
Be good.
Stop wasting time.
I've set up a barrier.
You will never get out.
(What is this?)
(That bad man)
(seems to like it.)
(Then I'll drink it all.)
Yin.
Don't do this.
I'll get you some food later.
Yin.
Why is your hair so long?
Who are you?
I'm asking you. Who are you?
The bell...
So you are Yin?
You've transformed!
Transformed?
I can even talk.
Why are you...
I am going to eat you.
You've just taken form
and you want to eat me?
You're so vindictive.
With your immortal power,
you can't defeat me.
You!
(Yantian Hall)
Master.
The Water Divine Beast has been extinct
for tens of thousands of years.
Without the source of its spiritual power,
the nourishment of the Xuan Lake,
it is extremely difficult
for it to survive and hatch,
let alone transform
in a short period of time.
That's why I felt deeply bad
when I heard Qing Yi's report
and came to tell you.
Yin, I am back.
Have you worn the new clothes
I sent you?
Why is there a pot?
Are you going to cook for me?
Yin!
Yin, you!
You look good in the new clothes.
What are you doing?
Put me down!
You're a newly transformed
immortal beast.
When did you learn
the Immortal-locking Spell?
You want my core?
Bad man!
Today
I am going to cook you up.
Cook me up?
You only remember
that I wanted your core, don't you?
Why don't you remember
how good I was to you?
I took care of you.
I hatched you.
After you took human form,
I gave you new clothes.
Why don't you remember all these?
Just put me down.
Let's talk.
No.
Anise.
Put some.
Cinnamon.
Bay leaf.
Put some.
Cumin, put some.
And tea leaves.
Everything.
Okay.
Put me in if you dare.
Come on.
Down there.
More fire.
Yin.
Put me...
When did you steal my Qiankun Pouch?
Stop it. Inside are some spirit talismans
and immortal artifacts.
If you don't use it properly,
it'll backfire on you.
Yin.
You...
What are you doing?
You naughty girl!
You're too young
to win me over.
Yin.
Don't use these talismans
indiscriminately.
It's a laughing
talisman.
Give it to me.
Yin.
Stop it!
Not this one!
It is an electric shock talisman.
Yin.
Come on.
Untie me!
No!
My bottom.
Yin, you!
Have you had enough?
You girl!
If I get serious,
you're done.
Don't you touch the knife.
The knife...
Yin!
You went too far.
Now that you've taken form,
we have to talk about
the laws of the Immortal Realm
and the morals of a gentleman.
To be honest,
I helped you hatch
from the egg, right?
Now, instead of repaying me
for raising you,
- you want to hurt me?
- Shut up! So noisy.
Let's go to the mountain.
I'll show you something better.
Shut up!
This brat
hasn't improved a bit.
He's being ruled by an immortal beast.
Xian Shan.
Shanmen Volume.
Master.
The bloody light on Jin's roster…
It is an omen
of the looming catastrophe.
He still hasn't dodged
the promise he made to Heaven Stone
to fulfill the catastrophe with himself.
This Water Divine Beast
is precisely his catastrophe.
Even after all the hard work,
he can't escape the God's will.
Gu Jin was formed from the heart blood
of True God Di Juan and True Goddess Yi He,
inheriting the most ancient
and pure Chaos Bloodline.
How could he be afraid
of a catastrophe brought about
by a Water Divine Beast?
The origin of the Water Divine Beast
is weird.
Even I
can't figure out her future with Jin.
If
she brought Jin
a catastrophe of death
and vanishment,
even a true god would not be spared.
How dare a worthless
low-level immortal beast
(Yantian Hall)
threaten God Yuan Qi?
Just kill it.
Xian Shan.
This is Lord Hong Chou,
the chief of Qingchi Palace.
She came from the God Realm
and was the one
who watched over God Yuan Qi as he grew up.
Greetings to Lord Hong Chou.
(Hong Chou, Chief of Qingchi Palace)
Donghua, you should know
that I stay in the Immortal Realm
and guard Qingchi Palace
only to wait for the day
when God Yuan Qi
returns to the divine throne.
I keep the Shanmen Volume
of Daze Mountain in my palm,
and I am always concerned
about God Yuan Qi's safety,
just because
I don't trust you.
Lord Hong Chou
is still so relentless.
It was because
you didn't stop God Yuan Qi in time
that he responded
to the catastrophe with himself
in exchange for the life of the Fire Phoenix.
If it was me back then,
I would rather go on the Heaven Path myself
than let God Yuan Qi
be damaged in the slightest.
Even though the Fire Phoenix lineage
is precious,
how can it compare
to the safety of God Yuan Qi?
Now the catastrophe is imminent,
why don't you
catch and dispose of
this low-ranking immortal beast
as soon as possible?
No way.
Immortal beasts are also living beings
in the Three Realms,
how can they be killed at will?
True Goddess Yi He
has long since issued an edict
that the order of the Three Realms
cannot be disrupted for God Yuan Qi.
This is against the laws of heaven,
and it will also jeopardize
God Yuan Qi's own destiny.
I can try
to avoid this catastrophe.
Okay.
Then take a try.
If your method fails,
I'll use mine
to dispose of the beast.
What do you want?
- Go.
- Why should I listen to you?
I'm not going anywhere.
Why don't you go?
Why should I listen to you?
What's this?
Four Perils, maybe.
Look what trouble you made.
Happy now?
Smart.
Fire talismans
are Four Perils' favorite.
What should I say about you?
Now is better.
But the talisman
probably won't last long.
What to do then?
But I...
Qiankun Pouch.
Cool?
Run!
Hurry up!
This way.
No. No.
Here.
No, this way.
This way.
Go.
Watch out!
Master, it is done.
I have bonded the two of them
with master-servant contract.
Water Divine Beast Yin
has become God Yuan Qi's
immortal servant.
The contract can be used
to resolve any grievances,
whether they be those of murder,
love, or grudge.
As long as the master-servant contract
remains intact,
God Yuan Qi will be safe?
That's right.
Master is at the peak of demigod,
almost becoming God Jin.
There are very few people
in the Three Realms
who can break
his master-servant contract.
Lord.
Don't worry.
Then let's keep this beast alive
for now.
I'll keep an eye
on God Yuan Qi's safety.
If this Water Divine Beast
dares to hurt him again,
I will no longer be polite to her.
- What did you just do to me?
- Why are you talking like me?
- You're the one talking like me!
Is it a trick?
Martial Uncle.
Qing Yi.
Why are you here?
Master asked me to come here to find you.
This is Yin?
She's being disciplined
by the master-servant contract.
Master-servant contract?
What is it?
Master has bonded you and Yin
with the master-servant contract.
She cannot think ill of you,
have delusional thoughts,
hurt you,
- or...
- Wait.
You mean
she'll never hurt me again?
Who gave you permission
to bind me
with the master-servant contract?
Or she'll be disciplined
like this.
Like this.
What is going on?
It's the same thing
with the master-servant contract.
She's restricted
to your immediate vicinity
and must do as she's told.
At my command?
Interesting.
Thank you, Master,
for saving me from suffering.
What's the noise?
You're still holding a knife.
You've been up all night.
So stubborn.
(My disciple.)
(It's time to come out.)
Master?
Get up.
Let's go.
The prohibition of the Forbidden Valley
has been lifted.
Could it be that the young Fire Phoenix
has returned?
Good luck for you.
You've just taken form
and you can go out.
Be obedient after getting out.
Understand?
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪