♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 3=
Master, Xian Zhu and I...
Master!
Slow down!
Greetings,
Master.
Xian Shan, Xian Zhu.
Come here, Gu Jin.
Let me take a good look at you.
You lost weight.
I lost weight? Really?
That is good.
You're Yin?
You've already tied me with this scoundrel
with master-servant contract,
but you don't know who I am?
I don't think so.
Yin,
show some respect.
This is my Master,
the Chief of the Daze Mountain.
So what if he's your master?
He just bullies me with his
high immortal power.
All of you are bullying me.
If I hadn't been tied to you
by the master-servant contract,
I would have reunited with my
Water Gelling Beast Clan
a long time ago.
The Water Gelling Beast Clan
was exterminated in the
Immortal-Devil War
seventy thousand years ago.
However, there is still
a distant relative of yours
alive in the Three Realms, the ancient
Water Divine Beast.
But if you want to reunite with your clan,
forget about it.
I have no family.
Yin,
I have tied you and Gu Jin
in a master-servant contract
due to fate.
It's not only beneficial
for Gu Jin
but also for you.
Currently,
I cannot
lift this contract,
but
as compensation,
I will give you a great gift.
Is Master using god power
to rebuild Yin's foundation
and immortal body?
This is an unparalleled opportunity/Nthat others can't even dream of.
The Water Gelling Beast Clan
has inherently weak immortal power.
If she cultivates on her own,
even after a hundred years,
there won't be much progress.
With Master's help,
her cultivation path
will be much smoother.
Yin,
I promise you that
if you help Daze Mountain
collect the immortal spirit
of the young Fire Phoenix
of the Wutong Island,
I will lift this contract for you.
You can also become a formal disciple
of the Daze Mountain.
Master.
Master, what do you mean?
Feng Yin has already
regained vitality.
Shouldn't her recondensed immortal spirit
automatically return to her body?
We thought so too.
But Feng Yin's immortal spirit has yet to return,
indicating that something went wrong.
It might be scattered across the Three Realms.
When I deduced it,
I sensed that
there is one portion of it
in our Daze Mountain.
However, I don't know
the exact location within the mountain.
If we can find this portion
of Feng Yin's immortal spirit,
we may trace
the remaining eight portions.
Master, I will search every corner
of the Daze Mountain
to retrieve this portion
of the immortal spirit.
As the chief, you can't back out of your promise.
If I help you find
the Fire Phoenix immortal spirit
and gather
the rest,
you must help me
break the master-servant contract
with this scoundrel.
No backing out.
However,
your cultivation is still shallow,
so there are many places in the Daze Mountain
that you cannot access.
You need to intensify your practice,
and then I can assist you in finding
the Fire Phoenix immortal spirit more quickly.
That's right.
The stronger your cultivation,
the less restricted you'll be by the contract.
Even if the master-servant contract remains.
you can separate and act independently,
making it much easier
to gather Feng Yin's
immortal spirit.
We can separate if we practice hard?
Yes.
This Moonlight Illusion cultivation method
is perfect for master-servant partners
to practice together.
Once you both master it,
with a shared understanding,
you can achieve a profound realm.
Keep practicing.
- Martial Uncle.
Everyone is here.
Martial Uncle, you've finally come out.
It's really unexpected that
after ten years of Forbidden Valley cultivation,
you've become so
extraordinary.
Yes, indeed!
What?
Extraordinary?
Him?
Yin, you're the same.
You are even more adorable
than what Qing Yi described.
You've transformed so quickly,
and you appear so beautiful.
Beautiful?
Her?
Yin, come here.
This is a welcome gift.
From today onwards,
we are a family.
Family?
Yes, one big family.
Come on, take it.
Accept it.
Oh, she took your gift first!
The ours too!
Everyone,
no need to give her gifts
just for my...
Mine is the most expensive.
Remember that.
And mine...
Thank you, thank you.
Take mine too.
Daze Mountain is so vast,
where do we start looking for
the Fire Phoenix immortal spirit?
Let's search little by little,
we'll eventually find it.
Let's take a look over there.
Over there.
There's nothing.
I can't see anything,
fly up a bit.
Still unclear,
move down.
Are you using me as your flying instrument?
If not for this master-servant contract,
I could fly much faster than you.
You think I want to use you?
You think I'm flying too slowly?
Fine,
let me show you.
What are you doing?
Accelerating.
Stupid Gu Jin!
- How's that? Fast enough?
- You scoundrel!
Gu Jin, Gu Jin, you...
How is it?
Is it fast enough now?
With your little ability,
without a flying talisman,
how high can you fly?
Where is this?
Never mind,
let's search. Once we find it,
we can all be free.
That'll be good.
You can hardly stand,
forget about the immortal spirit for now.
Let's have some rest first.
This is my residence.
Rest here, and we'll continue tomorrow.
Rest?
What did the Chief say?
He gave us cultivation techniques.
Are you treating them as waste paper?
The bright moon hangs in the sky,
the essence of heaven
and earth is at its purest.
It's the optimal time for cultivation.
If we don't search today,
we should focus on cultivation.
You just transformed into a human,
but you seem to know quite a bit.
When I hadn't transformed yet,
someone
was holding me
and talking about
things about the mortal realm and
cultivation techniques.
What are you saying?
Before transforming,
you could see outside.
It's sensing,
not seeing.
If I could see,
I would be blind now.
Before transforming,
I was manipulated by you.
Now, after transforming,
I'm still dragged around by you.
No,
we should
cultivate now.
Once my spiritual power is higher
due to the cultivation,
I won't be dragged around by you anymore.
Come on, let's go.
But what does that have to do with me?
I want to sleep.
See you.
What now?
Stupid Gu Jin,
just live your whole life
being a
good-for-nothing.
Being a good-for-nothing
is the lifelong dream of mine.
Bye.
If you're so lazy and aimless,
the Princess Hua Shu you're dreaming of
won't notice you.
How do you even know about Hua Shu?
You drank too much Drunken Jade Dew
and told me.
At the Fire Phoenix Birth Banquet,
the Peacock Clan princess
saved you,
saving you from embarrassment.
When you caught up
and saw her stunning beauty,
you were immediately captivated.
After that,
you couldn't think about anything else,
and she became
your everything.
Shut up.
I won't.
- Shut up now.
- I...
Let me tell you,
the things you said
can't be known by anyone
other than you and me.
Do you hear me?
If you don't agree,
then don't speak.
OK.
Listen,
in the future,
when you're dating
with Princess Hua Shu,
are you going to bring me along?
Indeed, I can't always
bring you, this burden, with me.
Then, let's practice together.
Are you ready
for practicing together?
I've been ready for a moment,
waiting for you.
Come on.
Don't move randomly.
I didn't.
(Free With a Clear Mind)
You are so childish! Don't move!
My buttocks!
What are you doing?
Chasing Dreams in the Clouds, Nine Heavens
as a Mirror.
Qian and Water is Kun, Li and Zhen
in all directions.
You got the Five Elements and
directions all wrong!
I was not wrong at all.
I made some adaption on the fly.
You don't understand.
You should follow
the designated positions.
First second you went Wind and Thunder,
and the next you went Li and Fire.
How am I supposed to know how you'll move?
First second you went Wind and Thunder,
and the next you went Li and Fire.
You're my immortal beast.
You should know
what's on my mind.
Why is there no understanding between us?
My big bed!
I missed you so much.
I missed you,
my big bed.
Why do you miss my big bed?
Get up.
What are you doing?
Are you going to sleep here too?
Of course, I have to sleep here.
You haven't progressed in your cultivation,
and we can't be apart.
I can only sleep here.
Yin,
if a man and a woman
are not an immortal couple,
sharing a bed
is inappropriate.
Understood.
So we are going to be an immortal couple?
Are you deliberately trying to make me angry?
When you were in beast form before,
you always slept on the ground.
I don't mind
sleeping together with you.
I'm going to the restroom.
I hope when I come back,
you're already asleep
on the floor.
What do you want?
I want to sleep on the bed.
Okay.
And
you have to cultivate seriously with me.
Alright.
You can't drag me around
in the air.
Okay.
And you can't make me serve tea,
massage,
- and...
- Okay.
I'll give you a detailed
set of rules later.
Starting today,
I won't order you around.
Can you turn around now?
Thank you.
Move a bit farther.
OK.
The 123rd rule:
Gu Jin,
you're not allowed...
There are already over a hundred rules!
- Enough!
- You can't...
Enough.
Let's press our fingerprints here.
(Yin)
The agreement is effective.
Alright,
I wish us a peaceful coexistence
and creating a beautiful life together.
Okay.
Since the agreement is settled,
let's follow the human customs.
We'll use the water bowl as a boundary,
one person facing the head of the bed,
and the other facing the foot,
no trespassing.
Can we sleep now?
We can,
but I...
OK.
I'm full now.
I'll take a nap.
Being dragged down by this fool,
how can I proceed on my immortal path?
Actually,
Martial Uncle Gu Jin,
apart from being mischievous,
unyielding when right,
lazy, and not proactive,
he's
not a bad person.
You don't need to be an immortal couple
with him for a lifetime.
Endure it and it will pass.
Immortal couple?
Qing Yi,
you've reminded me.
When I find
the Fire Phoenix immortal spirit,
I won't have to drag
this fool around anymore.
At that time,
I can control
my own destiny
and embark on the bright immortal path.
But what does that have to do with
immortal couple?
The Water Gelling Beast Clan
has already been
exterminated.
But I can revive
our clan.
The most important thing for revival
is vigorous reproduction of offspring.
Therefore,
I need to find an
outstanding male immortal with
excellent character, extraordinary appearance
who unconditionally supports me
in nurturing the Water Gelling Beasts,
to be my immortal partner.
This is the top priority,
right?
Right, right, right.
It sounds like a beautiful dream,
but in the Immortal Realm,
there are not many
male immortals
with exceptional talent like me.
Finding a second one
as lazy
and arrogant
as you
is indeed not easy.
Listen,
rest well,
and then we'll go find
Fire Phoenix Immortal spirit.
Got it?
(Demon Realm)
The Gate of Life and Death.
(Gate of Life and Death, Third Heaven,)
Life and death are decided by fate.
(Demon Realm)
Entering this gate is the only way
to enter the Third Heaven of the Demon Realm.
Sorry about this.
What are you doing?
I've told you before,
within the Gate of Life and Death,
the strongest from each generation of the
Demons gathers.
They are extremely powerful.
With your current strength...
If it weren't for you,
I would have broken through already.
Stop being willful.
Come back with me to the Jingyou Mountain.
As the heir to the Fox Clan,
you should learn to handle
some clan affairs.
Always running around outside...
Aunt, since you became the Fox Queen,
you like to put on an appearance of
devoting yourself to the Fox Clan.
But when Father was in dire straits
and asked you to return home,
how come you were only thinking about
entangling yourself with the second prince
of the Tiger Clan, Lin Mo?
Where were you
when Father and Mother
needed you the most
before their death on the battlefield?
Hong Yi,
during the Immortal-Demon War,
I couldn't return in time.
I regret it deeply.
So, Hong Yi,
for the sake of your parents,
I must take care of you.
Let me go!
I don't need you.
I've come so many times to
this dense forest of the Forbidden Valley.
If the Fire Phoenix immortal spirit were here,
I would have found it long ago.
Why bother coming here?
Maybe we'll find it.
I don't think so.
(Yu,)
(you've been here by yourself)
(for so long.)
(Are you scared?)
(Back then, we relied on each other)
(in the cave.)
(Who knew I would be picked up by
that scoundrel Gu Jin,)
(leaving you here alone.)
(But now you can rest assured.)
(I'll take you away.)
(Stay by my side.)
(I'll find a way)
(to help you transform.)
(Let's go.)
You actually hid
a Water Gelling Beast egg.
Come here!
Yu!
Slow down!
Yin, don't go over there.
Are you okay?
Don't go over there.
This is the aura of chaos.
It seems that this place
is the Sword Tomb arranged by the God Realm.
I'll go get it.
This aura...
This is the Chaos Sword Spirit formed by
Mother's Ancient Emperor Sword
after it fell into the Three Realms.
No wonder Mother
asked me to cultivate in the Daze Mountain.
It turns out she wanted
to use the power of chaos
to assist in my cultivation.
This blood of chaos
unexpectedly helped shape its sword body.
What's going on?
Is it going to recognize me as its master?
Sir,
I had no intention of trespassing.
I'll take my leave.
Yin, quickly leave!
Acknowledgment of the master!
The divine artifact
recognized you as its master?
Hey,
dude, listen,
come out now.
What are you doing?
You are such a lucky dog.
You should be happy.
His spiritual power is too strong.
If I accidentally ascend to godhood,
what should I do?
I don't want to ascend to godhood.
Why are you laughing?
You're not even a junior immortal yet.
You are safe.
I...
Sword gesture?
Come out.
Come out!
Come...
This is the mighty
divine artifact from earlier?
Weapons like this will change
along with the master's magical power.
Anyway, it recognized me as its master.
From now on, I'll call you Spirit Sword.
Look at this divine artifact.
It was so imposing just now,
but once in your hands,
it became like this.
You should think of ways to
- improve yourself?
- None of your business.
Water Gelling Beast's healing power?
And you are using it on me?
In gratitude
for saving
my sister just now.
What? Can't hear you.
Give my sister back to me.
It's gone.
What do you mean gone?
Where is it?
It's here.
Don't drop it again.
There's actually a
sycamore tree here.
What's wrong, Yin?
I feel like there's
something in this tree.
It's just a tree.
Could it be that
Feng Yin's immortal spirit...
It is actually
in a sycamore tree.
Master is going to ascend to godhood.
(Yantian Hall, Daze Mountain)
Master,
we found the immortal spirit.
One portion of young Fire Phoenix's
immortal spirit
has entered the Fire Phoenix Jade.
This portion of the immortal spirit
was found in the heart of
an ancient sycamore tree in the Sword Tomb.
The Phoenix Perching Sycamore Tree
has always been a universal truth.
But we didn't think of it.
The other eight portions of the immortal spirit
might also be in sycamore trees
outside of Wutong Island,
throughout the Three Realms.
The dispersed immortal spirit's
spiritual power is too weak
to return autonomously.
Only the Fire Phoenix Jade
can absorb young Fire Phoenix's
immortal spirit.
In other words,
as long as we can find
other ancient sycamore trees,
we can find the remaining portions of the
immortal spirit.
Ancient sycamore trees
are born from the spiritual power
of heaven and earth.
I only know
three of them.
One is
in the sacred land of the Fox Clan,
Jingyou Valley.
Another is
in the Abyssal Prison in the Ziyue Mountain.
The third is the place where the late
Heavenly Emperor
Chen Hui used to cultivate,
Guixu Mountain.
The others
need further exploration.
Now that we know the locations
of three ancient divine trees,
finding Feng Yin's immortal spirit
should be relatively easy.
Chief,
even though you have ascended to godhood,
don't forget the promise
you made to me.
We have made
a pact.
I won't forget.
When young Fire Phoenix's immortal
spirit reunites,
you will get what you desire.
However, the path ahead is perilous.
It depends on your karma and destiny.
Before I ascend to godhood,
I cultivated this immortal elixir
to help both of you enhance your immortal power.
Continue practicing
diligently every day in the future.
- Thank you, Master.
Jin,
this Sky-shrouding Umbrella
has been my magical tool
since I started cultivating.
No one
under half-godhood can damage it a bit.
Today, I'm giving it to you
to protect you.
Thank you, Master.
I'm going to the God Realm
and can't stay in the mortal realm anymore.
From now on,
you'll have to rely on yourselves.
Take care.
The physical body of young Fire Phoenix
is in the Soul Suppressing Pagoda.
I don't know how long it can last.
If the body dissolves
and the immortal spirit has nowhere to go,
then young Fire Phoenix
truly won't be able to come back.
Gu Jin,
you must hurry.
I understand, Master.
Martial Uncle, long time no see.
Indeed.
It's been a while since there were
so many people in Daze Mountain.
Master has great popularity.
Many came to congratulate him
on becoming a god.
Your master is so powerful.
Why do you look like a waste?
Why do I look like a waste?
Gu Jin.
Feng Ming,
you're here too.
Yes,
I came with Elder Feng Yun
to congratulate Donghua Immortal Lord.
I saw Heavenly Emperor Lan Feng
and the Four Immortal Lords from the
Heavenly Palace.
Do you know that
the immortal selection in the
Heavenly Palace is about to begin?
This time,
an important position
is currently vacant.
I am not gonna go.
You know
I'm never interested in these things.
Alright, then I won't take you
to meet them.
- See you around.
- See you.
The vacant immortal position,
can any immortal fill it?
Why?
What does it have to do with you?
Of course it has something to do with me!
I've read it in the
books about mortal realm.
If I want to revive
the Water Gelling Beast Clan,
I must obtain a position
in the Heavenly Palace.
Only then can I have a say
in the Immortal Realm.
With that,
I can secure
more benefits for our
Water Gelling Beast Clan.
There is no
Water Gelling Beast Clan anymore.
Like I said before, it's gone.
It will come back.
I'm telling you.
I'm confident.
After all, we've already found
one portion of Feng Yin's immortal spirit.
Once we gather all portions of it,
we can break the master-servant contact.
By then,
I can truly revitalize
our Water Gelling Beast Clan.
Fine.
There are so many immortals here.
My Record of Handsome Immortals
can finally come in handy.
(Record of Handsome Immortals)
What's this?
Let me see.
Record of Handsome Immortals.
I'm going to record all the male immortals
I like on it.
There's nothing in it.
You know nothing.
It hasn't started yet.
I must choose an male immortal
with the strongest power,
the most outstanding appearance,
and the best qualities
to be my partner.
It's so thick.
How many names are you going to record?
You're something.
Gentlemen,
I think we have met before,
maybe in the previous life.
Can you please
tell me your names?
Your friend?
Why are you laughing?
You scared them away!
Where did you learn
such a lousy flirting technique?
So foolish.
Let's go.
Sir,
I think we...
- Let's go.
- There are so many people here,
why did you use the master-servant contract?
Are you afraid others won't know?
You dare to talk
to any body.
Do you know who this person is?
Who is it?
I thought it was someone else.
It turns out
to be the long-lost
useless playboy.
Ling Feng,
long time no see.
Excuse me.
You are even with a
low-powered immortal servant.
But
it's quite right.
Back then,
this useless man
wanted to marry a beautiful lady.
Now,
this useless girl
has delusions
of climbing high.
You two are perfect for each other.
Don't you know your
own identity and status?
Why is he farting
in someone else's house?
it stinks.
Who are you?
Who is your master?
Who knows who you are?
What?
You tie a single braid,
thinking you're unique?
Interesting. Let's go.
You, a mere immortal servant...
I am sorry
if this fellow disciple of mine
offended you.
Let me introduce.
This is
the young master of Wanyi Mountain,
Mr. Ling Feng.
In terms of strength,
honestly speaking, he is on par with me.
We are both
wastes.
However,
when it comes to bragging,
I can't compare to him.
Our esteemed Mr. Ling Feng
is truly outstanding among the outstanding.
Gu Jin, you...
What?
Do you know where you are now?
You are at our Daze Mountain.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I can just say,
"Ling Feng hit me."
If each of the thousands of disciples of
Daze Mountain
give you one kick,
do you think you can still leave?
Hurry up and leave.
This is not over.
If only he could fell off the stairs.
You are here too.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Give me.
Give it to me.
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪