♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 4=
(Yantian Hall)
Lord Donghua ascended to the God Realm.
I'm here to congratulate him
on behalf of the Bainiao Island.
Your Highness,
thank you for coming.
My father should've come here
to congratulate him in person,
but he went to the battle
a while ago to defend the Bainiao Island,
and he hasn't recovered from his injury,
so he sent me.
May I
meet with Lord Donghua?
My Master has just ascended
to the God Realm.
He asked the two of us
to say goodbye
to everyone on his behalf.
Actually,
there's something else
that brought me here today.
I wonder if I can
borrow Lord Donghua's
Sky-shrouding Umbrella
to fend off the invasion of the Eagle Clan.
Hongque.
This is Peacock Feather Crown,
a holy treasure of our Peacock Clan.
We'd like to give it to Daze Mountain
in exchange of borrowing
the Umbrella for one year.
Your Highness,
I'm afraid we can't lend it to you.
Before my Master left,
he already gave the Umbrella
to Gu Jin.
The Umbrella is now Gu Jin's
personal weapon.
We can't speak for him.
Please try to understand, Your Highness.
Gu Jin.
Yin.
Thanks to my hard training,
my spiritual power improved again.
I can finally stay further
from that fool.
Can I take another step forward?
Where is she?
She's supposed to prepare
for going down the mountain tomorrow.
Where did she go?
So troublesome.
Yin.
Your Highness, why do you have
to go visit him in person?
You could just wait in the hall
and send a message,
and that Immortal Gu Jin
will come to visit you for sure.
With Lord Donghua ascending to the God Realm,
Senior Immortal Xian Shan
is now in charge of Daze Mountain.
And Gu Jin is the Chief Elder
of Daze Mountain.
There's nothing improper for me to visit him.
Immortal Gu Jin.
Are you Immortal Gu Jin?
Your Highness.
(Inaction)
Your Highness, long time no see.
You are really Immortal Gu Jin.
I'm here to pay you a visit.
Pay me a visit?
After we parted from Wutong Island,
I was going to come
to Daze Mountain to see you.
Unfortunately, our Peacock Clan
has been battling
against the Eagle Clan these years.
I had to stay with my father and help him.
That's why I couldn't come to visit you earlier.
So, you didn't
forget me.
It was destiny that made us meet.
How could I forget you?
But, I am surprised to see
that you are even more handsome now.
Am I?
Actually,
I'm here today
to thank you in person.
Thank me?
About the Immortal Feng's matter back then,
you kept it to yourself
that it was me who wanted
to see the Fire Phoenix Jade,
and you took full responsibility for the incident.
I really appreciate it.
Because of that,
you were punished
by the Heavenly Empress and Lord Donghua.
I've been feeling sorry for that.
I wasn't punished severely.
I was only grounded
by my Master for a little while.
By the way,
Your Highness,
did you receive the letters I sent you?
The letters?
Of course.
I keep them very well.
Then why didn't you…
The Eagle Clan
has been assaulting our Bainiao Island for years.
I've been caught up in battles
and worried about my clansmen,
so I was too occupied
to write back to you.
Hope you won't blame me.
Of course not.
How could I blame you?
The Peacock Clan…
Would you like to invite me inside
for a chat?
Sure.
Come on in.
Wait a sec.
You idiot Gu…
If you don't mind,
just call me by my name.
Then I'll call you Jin in the future.
So, this is
Princess Hua Shu.
No wonder Gu Jin
thinks about her all the time.
She's pretty indeed.
Jin, in fact,
I hope you can do me a favor.
Your Highness, please don't say that.
Just feel free to ask.
When we were on the Wutong Island,
you were so kind to help me,
and I always remember that.
As long as I can,
I'll do my best to help you.
Actually,
I want to borrow
the Sky-shrouding Umbrella from you.
The Sky-shrouding Umbrella?
I want to use it to defend
against the Eagle Clan's attack.
Only for one year.
One year later,
I'll return it
back to you intact.
No, don't.
You can't lend her the Umbrella.
Yin,
where were you?
I looked for you everywhere.
Sorry to ask, but this is…
This is Yin.
My Master took her in as a disciple
before he ascended to the God Realm.
She's my junior sister.
Lord Donghua hasn't
accepted disciples for years.
I didn't expect he'd take in one
right before he left.
Immortal Yin,
nice to meet you.
Your Highness,
with all due respect,
we can't lend you the Umbrella.
Yin.
Gu Jin needs to keep it for use.
He can't lend it.
Jin,
I know the Umbrella
is no ordinary treasure,
and that you can't lend it for no reason.
But the Bainiao Island
is in a life-or-death crisis right now.
Our clansmen are suffering heavy losses.
I can't save our clan
all by myself.
Jin, for old times' sake, please…
Your Highness,
to tell you the truth,
Gu Jin is about to leave the mountain
for the Demon Realm
to look for the Fire Phoenix's immortal energy
that he shattered by accident.
My Master gave him the Umbrella
for self-protection
because he can't even set up
the most basic
Moonlight Illusion Formation.
He hasn't even reached
the level of Junior Immortal.
- Yin.
- Your Highness…
Your Highness,
don't listen to her nonsense.
It's not nonsense.
You are lazy and slack
in training every day.
You really think you are
tough enough to defend yourself?
Do you?
It's not like what you said.
Your Highness,
I know…
I know you are worried about your clansmen,
but could you also worry
about Gu Jin's safety?
If you take
the Umbrella away,
it'll be like…
plucking hair from the head of…
of a bald man.
Yes, a bald man.
You've only learned a few mortal idioms,
and you aren't using it right.
- It's the truth.
- Jin.
I didn't know
Lord Donghua gave you the Umbrella
for self-protection.
I guess I put you in a difficult position.
Your Highness, please don't say that.
Sorry to bother you.
I'll leave now.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Take care, Jin.
Your… Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Come back.
What are you doing?
- Yin, you…
- I've told you,
- You can't lend it.
- Your Highness.
- Wait for me. I'll walk you out.
- Seriously, you can't lend it.
Yin, stop messing around.
Let me walk you out.
Your…
Could you stop already?
I can't believe how narrow-minded you are.
You enjoy using the master-servant contract
to trick me,
so I'm using it
to make you run.
I stopped you from lending the Umbrella
because
I know your cultivation base is low
and you can't defend yourself.
I did it for your own good.
Enjoy your running.
I'll go to bed now.
Enough is enough.
Don't go. You…
Yin, Yin.
This is…
Yin,
why are you running this late?
Working out?
Yes.
I've been
working out a lot lately.
I… I like
to run like this.
Look, these are the biographies
of the well-known immortal beasts
in the Three Realms you asked for.
Take a look.
Here, give me.
- Right here. Here you go.
- Give me.
When I was A Pet in the Heavenly Palace.
No, it won't work.
The Stories
between Me and My Master.
Not gonna work either.
Useful Tips
for Taming My Master.
I heard…
I heard the writer of this book
not only helped his Master
successfully ascend to the God Realm
through his hard work,
but also trained himself
into a senior immortal.
He's got great reputation
in the immortal beasts' world.
"Restrained by the rules
of the master-servant contract,
spiritual beasts
cannot fight the contract forcibly."
I'm exhausted.
"Don't be afraid to think outside the box.
Cater to his tastes
and humor his needs
by praising and encouraging him."
Would you like to take a break?
No.
I'll keep this one.
You can go back now.
I'll keep running.
Alright.
(The entrance, Daze Mountain)
What took you so long?
I've been waiting for you.
Why don't you try running the whole night?
Let's go.
(According to the book,)
(I can't openly defy the master of the contract.)
(Instead, I should cater to his tastes)
(to get what I want.)
(Let me give it a try.)
You've been saying that you wanted
to try the mung bean cake from the mortal world.
I learned how to make it
and made some for you last night.
Try it.
You put poison in it, didn't you?
Why would I do that?
I want to apologize to you
for yesterday.
Really?
You made it yourself?
Or what?
Tastes good?
Not bad.
Then about yesterday…
Whether or not
I'll forgive you depends on your behavior.
Make more of this when you have time.
Let's go.
Come on.
Coming.
(He forgave me already?)
(Are you kidding?)
(The tips for taming)
(worked very well.)
Jin, Yin.
Senior brother.
Why are you all here?
You don't have to see us off.
We only go down the mountain
to fetch the immortal energy.
We'll be back soon.
And my spiritual power
has improved a lot.
I can protect myself and her.
Yin,
make sure to protect Jin well.
We'll count on you.
You got it.
I will take good care of him.
Rest assured.
Jin,
according to Master's instructions,
Hong Ruo, the Demon Lord of the Fox Clan,
is very close to Feng Yuan,
the Heavenly Empress,
so you guys can go to the Fox Clan
in the Jingyou Valley
of the Demon Realm to find the parasol tree first,
and then head to Ziyue Mountain.
Understood.
The Immortal and the Demon Realms have been
holding a deep grudge against each other.
When you enter the Demon Realm,
you've got to be extra cautious.
Got it.
We are leaving.
Have a safe trip.
Let's go.
Congratulations
on breaking through the Gate of Life and Death
and entering the Third Heaven.
(Back then, my parents)
(fell into the immortals' trap)
(and died in the battle.)
(The Nirvana Wheel was also taken.)
(Heize Pool, the Third Heaven, the Demon Realm)
(I must forge a weapon)
(in this Heize Pool for myself,)
(and then go to the Immortal Realm)
(to get the Nirvana Wheel back.)
The Nirvana Wheel.
Those in the Three Realms
who swallow the energy of their own kind
will fall and become devils.
Once a year,
the Half-god Demon Dragon
that guards the Abyssal Prison
(The Barrier entrance, Abyssal Prison)
will drive the newfound devils
into the prison.
I want you
to lure Hong Yi
into the prison at that time.
(Abyssal Prison)
He's mine.
My son,
go under the parasol tree in the southeast.
It's a tree from the God Realm.
The devils can't hurt it.
(Jingyou Valley, the Second Heaven, the Demon Realm)
How is it going?
(Hong Mei, Elder of the Fox Clan)
I sent someone to follow His Highness secretly.
But he suddenly disappeared as soon
as he broke into the Third Heaven.
Have you asked our allies
in the Third Heaven?
I have.
How could this happen?
I'm Hong Ruo of the Fox Clan
in the Jingyou Mountain.
I came to Ziyue Mountain for an urgent matter.
Ziyue Mountain
is True God Di Juan's cultivation place.
He has returned to the Ancient God Realm.
No visitors.
But I…
(The Demon Realm)
So, this is the Demon Realm.
- I think…
- Shh.
Lower your voice, will you?
Don't blame me for not warning you.
The Immortal Realm and the Demon Realm
don't get along.
Your healing power
is quite weak.
You got to be careful, or a demon will attack you,
take your internal core, and devour you.
Got it?
Based on the story books,
there are a lot of dashing
and handsome demon lords here.
Is that true?
Look at you, so ignorant.
Those handsome demons you talked about
are all powerful demons
who've entered the Second Heaven
through cultivation,
so they can take on attractive appearances.
While those ordinary small demons
can't take on human forms at all.
They can be very ugly.
So, which level are we on right now?
The Second Heaven.
In that case,
I do have a chance
to see some handsome demon lords.
Do you still remember
why we came here?
We are here to look
for the immortal energy of Feng Yin.
You look like you are here for a date.
Don't talk nonsense.
If I were to date someone,
I'd chose a guy from the Third Heaven.
The Third Heaven?
The Third Heaven
is the place where the Demon King lives.
But the Ziyue Mountain we are heading
is actually in the Third Heaven.
Shall I introduce you
to the Demon King?
Why…
Why did you reveal your original form?
Change your form back, now.
If you get caught,
I won't be able to get you back.
Hurry, change back.
I can't help.
The demonic power
in the mountain is too overwhelming.
One hundred years ago,
the Fox Queen Hong Ruo started to rise.
Under her leadership, the Fox Clan
became the biggest clan in the Demon Realm.
This place is not to be underestimated.
Your comments on our Fox Clan
makes me feel flattered.
Come here.
This demon's got high spiritual power.
I bet he's long sensed
our immortal aura.
We must be careful.
Will he find out about me?
No.
Before we left,
I asked Xian Shan to cast a spell on you.
In outsiders' eyes,
you are just
a spiritual cat.
A spiritual cat.
- I…
- Shh.
I'm Hong Huo.
May I know who are here
to visit our Jingyou Mountain?
We are Gu Jin and Yin
from Daze Mountain.
We are here to visit Hong Ruo, the Fox Queen.
So, you are Lord Donghua's disciples.
In that case,
please come with me.
Let's go.
Careful. Don't run around.
So beautiful.
Stop it.
The disciples of the Daze Mountain
are trained to be righteous and moral.
They won't be easily enchanted.
Remove the spell.
Let's go.
I'm Gu Jin of Daze Mountain.
Greetings, Your Highness,
Elders.
Gu Jin.
You've grown up.
Shouldn't you go look
for the immortal energy of Feng Yin?
What did you come here for?
Actually, that's exactly the reason
why I'm here.
This is part of the immortal energy
of Feng Yin I found in a parasol tree
by accident.
My Master told me
that the rest of the pieces
might scatter in the parasol trees
in all Three Realms,
including
the one in the Jingyou Valley of the Fox Clan.
So, Your Highness,
I hope you can let me
enter the Jingyou Valley
and take a look.
That's ridiculous.
The Jingyou Valley is a holy place of our clan
where we breed young.
How could we let you, an immortal,
get close to it?
Even if Lord Donghua
came here in person today,
we wouldn't let him enter,
let alone you.
We promise we'll only fetch the energy piece.
We will not touch the parasol tree.
Your Highness,
on the account
of the Heavenly Empress Feng Yuan
and the Wutong Island,
please allow me to try.
(Because of him,
my precious disciple Feng Yuan)
(lost all her immortal energy back then.)
(I can't believe he can still manage)
(to get the support
from Feng Yuan and Dong Hua.)
(I'm afraid he's not as simple as he seems.)
(Since I can't go into the Ziyue Mountain,)
(maybe this kid has a way)
(of entering it.)
It's not impossible
for you to enter the Jingyou Valley.
But you aren't our clansmen,
I can't make the exception for you
for no reason
even on the account
of Feng Yuan.
Then, Your Highness,
what do you want from us?
Yin.
You are quite smart.
My nephew Nine-tailed Fox Hong Yi
went missing in the Ziyue Mountain a while ago.
If you can help me find him back,
I'll allow you
to enter the Jingyou Valley.
Hong Yi went missing in the mountain?
That's right.
In the Third Heaven,
where the origin of Hong Meng
of the Demon Realm is at.
The Demon Realm.
What do you think?
Alright.
There's also
a parasol tree in the Ziyue Mountain,
where we are going to visit anyway.
I'd like to help you find your nephew back.
Then it's a deal.
I'll stay here
and wait for you to bring Hong Yi back.
What kind of a place the Ziyue Mountain is?
Why is everybody afraid of it?
The Ziyue Mountain
is the place where Di Juan,
one of the two True Gods,
used to dwell.
The Purple Moon he had
was the power source
of the entire Demon Realm.
So, the demons were all afraid of him.
Besides, there's a powerful Barrier
protecting the mountain.
Those who trespass on it
will be torn apart by the power of the Barrier.
In that case,
how are we supposed to get in?
Princess Hua Shu.
How dare you
(Yan Shuang, the Princess of the Eagle Clan)
steal from us?
Hand over the Blue Blood Reishi.
No way.
The Reishi.
Your Highness.
Sky-shrouding Umbrella.
Your Highness, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Come on.
Five against one.
It's so unfair.
Who are you?
Gu Jin of Daze Mountain.
Yin of Daze Mountain.
Fine.
I, Yan Shuang, will remember you two.
Let's go.
Thank you, Jin.
Don't mention it.
Your Highness,
who are
those people?
Why did they fight you over that thing?
My father's immortal energy was damaged
after fighting the Eagle King.
In the Three Realms,
only the Blue Blood Reishi
can heal his injury.
To kill my father, the Eagle Clan
kept trying to take it from me,
or destroy it if they can't have it.
The Eagle Clan has gone too far.
The one you saw
is Yan Shuang, the Princess of the Eagle Clan.
As the Princess
of the Bainiao Island,
I've never thought
I'd be bullied like this.
Your Highness,
you are injured.
Let's find an inn
so you can take a rest.
Your Highness,
put this on.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Let's go.
It's quite warm, isn't it?
Careful.
Your Highness, rest well.
We'll leave now.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Your Highness, you are suffering
from an internal injury.
You need to take some spiritual herbs.
Yin,
go get some spiritual herbs.
Me?
I need to stay here and take care of her.
Go on.
Thank you, Yin.
I really appreciate it.
You are welcome.
Come back soon.
But,
Your Highness, you've long reached
the level of Junior Immortal, right?
How come your spiritual power is still weak?
The Eagle Clan has been fighting me
over the Blue Blood Reishi,
and my father's life is in danger.
I had to use my own spiritual power
to protect my father's Spiritual Core.
Then how are you supposed to defend yourself?
I can't worry about that for now.
I've got to go back.
Otherwise, the Eagle Clan
will attack our island again
if they find out I'm not there.
Gu Jin is such an idiot.
He totally threw himself
at her feet as soon as he saw her.
He'll be in big trouble.
But it's none of my business.
Let him be.
There's nothing I can do anyway.
Jin.
Didn't I just walk past here a minute ago?
Your Highness,
you aren't recovered yet.
Even if you go back now, you still can't…
I must do whatever it takes
to protect
my clansmen.
Worse comes to the worst,
if I agree to marry
into the immortal clan of the South Sea,
our Bainiao Island
will no longer
be supportless
and helpless like this.
How could you agree to such an arrangement
at the cost of your own happiness?
I'll only go for it
as the last resort.
You don't have to worry.
I've been training hard lately.
Maybe
I can find a shortcut
to improve my cultivation base quickly.
At that time,
the Eagle Clan will have to stand down.
Your Highness,
I'll lend you
the Sky-shrouding Umbrella.
I think with the protection
of the Umbrella barrier,
your clan can absolutely
defend against the enemy.
Jin.
Don't look at me like this.
Just an umbrella. It's no big deal.
What matters right now is to solve the crisis
that the Bainiao Island is facing.
Please take it.
I really appreciate
your kindness and help.
Jin.
I'm here.
Yin.
Where are you?
This inn is like a maze.
So dumb.
Master-servant contract?
Isn't Yin
Lord Donghua's
registered disciple?
How come…
Yin's spiritual power is weak,
so my Master asked me to protect her
in this way.
Yin has never
left Daze Mountain before.
She has no any sense of direction.
I may as well just summon her back directly.
I see.
Come back.
You are so silly.
How could you get lost
in a small inn like this?
Couldn't you find your way?
No, I…
Here you go.
Alright,
stay here.
Don't run around anymore.
Your Highness,
I'll let the waiter
to decoct the medicine for you.
Thank you.
What are you looking at?
Take care of Her Highness.
Your Highness, would you like some water?
No need.
I still have things to do. I've got to go.
Hold on.
He went to decoct the medicine for you.
If he comes back and sees that you've left,
he'll go through the trouble for nothing.
Why don't you wait for him?
You can leave after he's back.
I don't need a servant like you
to tell me what to do.
He told you that?
How I talk to your master
and what we talk about
is none of your concern.
As a servant,
you should focus on doing your job right.
The medicine is ready.
Where's Princess Hua Shu?
She left.
Left?
She… She's still wounded.
Yin, I told you to keep her stay.
How?
As a servant,
I should focus on my own job.
Do I have the right to interfere in the matter
between my master and the princess? No.
What's wrong?
Why are you mad?
Did I do something?
Why did you tell Hua Shu
about the master-servant contract thing?
Because you were looking for me.
I wanted to summon you back,
so I uttered the spell,
and Hua Shu saw it through.
Don't worry.
Princess Hua Shu is pretty and kind.
She wouldn't think too much of it.
She just…
She…
Pretty and kind.
Back then on the Wutong Island,
she helped me
when she didn't even know me.
Apparently, she's a kind-hearted person.
Come on, don't be mad.
Yin.
Actually,
I got hurt too
when I tried to save her.
It really hurts.
You deserve it.
Good.
I feel much better now.
I knew
our Yin
still cared deeply about me.
Not really.
I was just worried that you'd slow me down.
You big fool.
All you can think about
is Hua Shu.
You got hurt for saving her life,
yet she left
without even saying goodbye to you.
Don't you think it's strange?
She's worried about the Bainiao Island.
You still need to go
to the Ziyue Mountain for a mission.
You don't have time
to concern about the Bainiao Island.
How could you…
Look how worried you are.
Alright,
I'll
stop pretending.
Yes,
it's true that ordinary people
dare not approach the Ziyue Mountain,
but I'm no ordinary person.
I'm very resourceful.
With my power and strength,
I can easily
take you into
the Ziyue Mountain.
Really?
You bet.
I'll be damned if I believe you.
You don't? Come with me.
I'm not going.
Why not? Come on.
I'll show you
my true power.
So, this is the Ziyue Mountain.
The demonic aura here is so strong.
No matter ordinary immortals and demons
dare not to get close to it.
Tell me about it.
Without permission,
ordinary half-gods aren't allowed in at all.
But it's different
when it comes to me.
Watch.
You'll just go in like this?
Or what?
Don't worry.
I've got a trump card.
But you should at least prepare a visiting note.
It's rude for you to go in like this.
Who are you?
How dare you trespass on the Ziyue Mountain?
It's you,
you three-headed guy.
Don't you recognize me?
Watch your mouth.
I'm the Dragon Lord guarding the mountain.
You are insolent and impudent.
Get lost, now.
This is the trump card you talked about?
I…
I know Bibo.
Bibo.
Stop.
(Bibo, Water Divine Beast)
You stupid dragon.
Are you blind even with six eyes?
If you hurt my…
The cousin of the neighbor
of the distant nephew of my seventh aunt,
I'll make you pay for it.
(Three-headed Fire Dragon)
- I'm also…
- Are you alright?
I'm fine.
My nephew,
it's been over 100 years.
You finally came to visit me.
I missed you so much.
Give me a hug.
I'm also… I…
Bibo.
Have you ever seen
a Nine-tailed Fox in the Ziyue Mountain?
(Bibo Hut, the Ziyue Mountain)
I've searched telepathically,
and there are no traces
of a Nine-tailed Fox here.
No?
How's that possible?
The Fox Queen Hong Ruo was pretty sure
that her nephew went into the Ziyue Mountain.
If he's not here,
how are we supposed to go to the Jingyou Valley
to find the immortal energy of the Fire Phoenix?
Bibo,
before my Master ascended to the God Realm,
he told me there's also
a parasol tree in the Ziyue Mountain.
There is one.
But,
why do you ask?
The Fire Phoenix's immortal energy
shattered because of me.
My Master said her immortal energy
could scatter in the parasol trees.
You want me to take you
to the tree?
That's right.
No.
We can't go there.
Why not?
Because the parasol tree in the Ziyue Mountain
is not at a usual place.
It's in
the Abyssal Prison.
The Abyssal Prison?
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪